[{"answer": "You can sing later.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Can I sing later?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Mr. Showbiz?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "How are you, daddy?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I never sleep.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Are you getting much sleep?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Are you a good nappy changer?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes, there you go.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "ORGAN: Diapers?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "You're a good diaper changer?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I'm loving it, man.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "You're liking being a dad?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "I've got three boys.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "I mean, you can -- you can give me some advice on fatherhood, right?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes, because I -- I was neglectful when I saw you at \"America's Got Talent,\" because you were too busy.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "-- than me.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "You're a sports fan, right?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes, no one knew who you were in America.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Because your running joke with me, of course, is it was being -- I'm not famous, right?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Does that sicken you?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "You're threatening me with physical violence, aren't you?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Every --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Do you wake -- I'm going to ask you this -- do you wake up some mornings and just think, \"Good God, I am lying next to Mariah Carey\"?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "-- this is permanent, this is real?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I was so sure because that was Mariah Carey.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Why were you so sure?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I don't think she did.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Did she know that she was your dream girl?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Me, dammit.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "But who's the boss at home?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Yes, that's a --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "I mean, that's how you get to the top, isn't it?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes, four hours.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "ORGAN: You're doing it for four hours, right?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "One-thirty -- and I'm probably in the studio until about 7:30.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "You get up at 1:00 -- you're on air at 1:30?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I don't sleep, man.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "When do you sleep?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "No, maybe two hours a night.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Do you sleep much at all?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Because it becomes very contagious, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "It's all how it's handle, in my opinion.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "ORGAN: Do you have any credibility issues with the way that stars are found on these talent shows?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "And we do see competitors coming on and trying it on, don't we?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "This is like his second hundred million dollar deal, right?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "When you see people becoming instantly very famous on this show, how do you feel, as somebody who's in that bubble of fame?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I do -- I just hope they know what they're in store for, because I would say if you weigh it out, the things -- the good things about fame are probably smaller than the bad things about fame, especially if you don't know how to handle it, because it's a magnifying glass.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Do you worry about that?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Oh, man!", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Where do you draw the line, the parity, because you're both very famous?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "There is, but if you give them enough, if you -- if you feed the sharks, they won't attack you.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Is there a line that can still be drawn if you do that, do you think, in terms of personal privacy?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I hate it, man.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "When you see other celebrities moaning about being famous, what do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "There really is none, but if I had to, I would say honesty plus confidence.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "If you could simplify it for somebody, what's the secret of being a good stand-up?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "It's -- everything is topical to me, because a lot of it is about my life.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "How much of your act is topical?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Yes, I got to DJ his inauguration party.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "-- you got a great honor, didn't you?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Now, it was amazing.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "How did that feel?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I think he's doing phenomenal.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't -- he'd -- he'd have too many bodyguards around him.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "ORGAN: -- would you -- would you take him out?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I think there was a time where --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Because you've wanted to, haven't you?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "If you were entering the show --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "What is my talent?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "Your wife is great.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "What are you saying singing?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Oh, man, I could --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "What would you actually do -- other than stand-up comedy, what would you do if you walked on stage on \"AGT\"?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "You want a freestyle?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Well, before I got on this show, it was very boring.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "How good are you?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "No, it's absolutely phenomenal.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Can you quite believe what's happened to you?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "That is amazing.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "And I love that it's an overnight sensation, but it took me 32 years to get there, you know?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Well, I was always a singer, and I had a band for about 15 years, and I was the lead singer of the band, and I would do impressions of singers.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "What was the act?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "And that was the magical tipping point, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "You can sing later.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Can I sing later?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "No, no, never.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Do you ever regret losing the anonymity?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "Of course, I'm the guy who spends all his money.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Tell me I'm wrong, Winston was always about the money, right?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "So, do you want to perform?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "That's what he wants to hear.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "Can I do the Roy Orbison?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "I'm very happy.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "Are you pleased with it?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "This is something I've worked my whole life to get to.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 858, "question": "Is it the culmination of the dream for you?", "qSentId": 857}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 873, "question": "And in many ways, saved the kind of life you may have had, right?", "qSentId": 872}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, she's still around and she --", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "Was she around to see that?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "RIMM: She's having probably the best of time, more than anyone.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "What does she make of it?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "Well, you know, if someone can do it in the family, I'm sure they would.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 909, "question": "Amazing thing to be able to do that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 908}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 918, "question": "It's called \"Michael Grimm,\" right?", "qSentId": 917}, {"answer": "I'm going to sing a song off the album.", "docId": "110530pmt", "aSentId": 936, "question": "What are you going to sing?", "qSentId": 935}]